JAMES STEWART

Senior Full Stack Developer

@ james.leo9042@gmail.com ♥ Singapore 520147. Blk 147 Tampines Avenue 5.

SUMMARY

With 5 years of experience as a Full Stack Developer, I have collaborated with various companies including small startups and large communities.

This has given me a deep understanding of the entire web lifecycle, from initial architecture to final deployment.

I have dedicated much of my career to developing an improved problem-solving approach for difficult tasks, as well as staying updated on new technologies and tools when necessary.

Love to work with great people, inspiring others, being inspired, and mentoring others.

EXPERIENCE

Web Development

05/2020 - 07/2020

Adesso SE

Leipzig, Germany

Adesso SE is a software development and IT consulting company based in Leipzig, Germany. With its headquarters in Dortmund, the company has a strong presence in Leipzig and operates globally. Adesso SE specializes in providing innovative solutions and services in the areas of digital transformation, agile software development, and IT consulting.

 As a web developer I attended in real development projects for provide of delivering software solutions across various industries, such as digital transformation journeys by innovative software solutions, developing ecommerce platforms for clients in retail, manufacturing and other industries, and creating mobile applications, cloud platforms, and data analytics tools.

Web Application Development

04/2019 - 07/2019

Adesso SE

Leipzig, Germany

Adesso SE is also committed to sustainability and social responsibility, actively supporting various initiatives to make a positive impact in the communities it operates in.

 As a web application developer I attended in application development of healthcare sector, such as electronic health records(EHR) systems, telemedicine applications, and health data management. During that time, I got my experience that can provides IT solutions same these.

LANGUAGES

English Proficient ••••

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

2013 - 2017

Singapore Institute of Technology (SIT)

10 Dover Dr, Singapore 138683



SKILLS

Languages

JavaScipt · TypeScript · Node.js ·

ECMAScript(ES6) · HTML · CSS ·

PHP · Java · Python

Library

React · jQuery · D3.js · Anime.js

Framework

Redux · React Native · Angular · Vue ·

Bootstrap · Tailwind CSS · Laravel ·

Codelgniter · Django

Database/Storage

MongoDB · MySQL · PostgreSQL ·

Firebase · Amazon S3 ·

Google Cloud Storage

Tool Git

GitHub · GitLab · Bitbucket · Jira

Blockchain Tech

Blockchain · Ethers.js · Web3.js ·

 $\mathsf{Solana} \cdot \mathsf{Cosmos} \cdot \mathsf{EVMOS} \cdot$

Blockchain APIs · Moralis

Other

Web development ·

Responsive Design · Web Sockets ·

User Experience(UX) ·

Software Development · HTTP · Ajax